question_data = [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the &quot;Shrek&quot; film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The United States Department of Homeland Security was formed in response to the September 11th attacks.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Rugby League, performing a &quot;40-20&quot; is punished by a free kick for the opposing team.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
